var title = "Numbers 0 to 10";

var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "zero (0)",
    answer: ["μηδέν"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "one (1)",
    answer: ["ένα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "two (2)",
    answer: ["δύο"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "three (3)",
    answer: ["τρία"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "four (4)",
    answer: ["τέσσερα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "five (5)",
    answer: ["πέντε"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "six (6)",
    answer: ["έξι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "seven (7)",
    answer: ["επτά", "εφτά"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "eight (8)",
    answer: ["οκτώ", "οχτώ"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "nine (9)",
    answer: ["εννιά", "εννέα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "ten (10)",
    answer: ["δέκα"],
    partial: [],
  },

];
  